Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/harshit-jain-bb51292a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

SAPUI5

С

C++

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Hindi (Full Professional)

Honors-Awards

Best Outgoing Sportsperson
Best Sports Captain
Spot Award
Geek of the Month

Harshit Jain

Frontend Engineer @ Intuit | Ex MakeMyTrip, SAP | JavaScript | React | UX | UI

Bengaluru

Summary

Experienced Software Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the Computer Software Industry. Skilled in JavaScript, React, React Native, SAPUI5, OData, HTML & CSS. Strong engineering professional with a B.Tech focused in CSE from Jaypee Institute of Information Technology.

Experience

Intuit
Software Engineer 2
July 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months)
Bangalore

MakeMyTrip.com Senior Software Developer May 2018 - July 2019 (1 year 3 months) Gurgaon, India

Helped MakeMyTrip to venture into a new line of business called 'Experiences' by developing the mobile app for both Android and iOS using React & React Native from scratch by writing scalable and robust code. Key achievements have been below

- Developed 3 out of 6 funnel pages of the app.
- Worked on critical features of the experiences funnel like 'Coupon and Discounting', 'Payment Integration' etc.
- Collaborated with the Product Manager and Designer to create the best possible user experience for the end user.

SAP

4 years

Senior Consultant - Development April 2018 - May 2018 (2 months) Gurgaon, Haryana, India Consultant - Development June 2014 - March 2018 (3 years 10 months) Gurgaon, India

Majorly worked on projects related to IS-OIL & GAS (Industry specific oil and gas solution), HCM and CRM domain of SAP Products.

University of Notre Dame Research Intern May 2013 - August 2013 (4 months) South Bend, Indiana, USA

I was majorly working on developing an android application to improve medical adherence among elderly patients suffering from chronic diseases. The aim was to develop a user friendly application to ensure that they take their prescribed medications on time, get new medications ordered timely and also to record their happiness levels through small quizes.

Engineers India Limited Intern May 2012 - July 2012 (3 months) New Delhi, India

Worked on a module of EIL's Employee Portal System.

Indian Institute of Technology, Gandhinagar Intern May 2011 - July 2011 (3 months) Gandhinagar, Gujarat, India

Worked on developing an an Intelligent traffic light system algorithm which will reduce traffic congestion.

Education

Jaypee Institute of Information Technology B.Tech, CSE · (2010 - 2014)

Mother Teresa Public School